



ABOUT ME

My name is Janice Chen. I live in the city of Riobamba, Ecuador. I was born in Los Angeles, California and I am a Taiwanese descent. All of my cultural wealth has allowed me to speak and develop widely with 4 languages with which I have been able to translate simultaneously, thus reaching connections with other brands and facilitating the development of new businesses.

My professional experience is in the field of web design, photography and advertising graphics designing with tools such as illustrator and photoshop as well as branding and management of the design. In my free time I dedicate myself to content for design and entertainment for the Twitch platform.



NAME Janice Chen

CEL +593 960950555

EMAIL janicechen31997@hotmail.com

L HABILITIES

DEVELOPER





EDUCATION



University:

• Graphic Design Universidad Nacional De Chimborazo



Master

• Magister in Design mention Design Management





EXPERIENCE

September 2020-Today 2022

Graphic designer for the political party Reto 33

July 2020 - Present 2022

Community manager and advertising designer at

Tian Yuan Cultural Center

2021 - 2022

Content creator

2019 - 2020

Graphic Designer for the Democratic Left political.

November 2020- December 2021

Web designer, UI/UX for Eduland

2019 - 2022

Freelance Graphic Designer

2017 - 2018

Rights Protection Council -

Human Mobility (Municipality, Riobamba).

Volunteer at Hult Prize Regionales (Quito, Ecuador).

Graphic Designer at Fundesec

